[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":40483,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":68447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":35669,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":104121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":19277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":123400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":19319,"trial_type":"feedba ck","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":142721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":9550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":152272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":4055,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":156328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and  then ad d the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":6303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":162632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2238,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":164871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":170359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1695,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":172055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":176247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correc t! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1758,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":178007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":184311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1399,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":185711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<s ub>6</su b> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":189087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1806,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":190896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtrac t 6 to g et your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":194559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":195823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":199943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":201375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3556,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":204932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1257,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":206191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":19778,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":225974,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarl y, 3 is  its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":33413,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":259388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":27197,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":286589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1869,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":288462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under  +<sub>6< /sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6510,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":294973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1630,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":296605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":302133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1434,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":303569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4954,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":308525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 i s the id entity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1334,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":309860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":11279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":321140,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":25215,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":346356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and t he opera tion can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":20622,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":366980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub> 6</sub>  2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":79534,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":446516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":29946,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":476467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":7062,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":483530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<su b>6</sub >? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":39614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":523146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":3829,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":526978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<su b>6</sub >? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":43437,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":570417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":572721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":9574,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":582297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1550,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":583848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedbac k to mak e sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":21839,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":605688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":6717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":612407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1671,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":614081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":5348,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":619431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":624538,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":6979,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":631520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":637280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":641032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":12922,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":653955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted from the total so the result is 5.","explanation_history":["Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9 the result","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9 ","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted the","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted th","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted t","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted from the total so the reul","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted from the total so the reu","Added 4 and 1 which makes 5. Since 5 is less than 9, 9 is not subtracted from the total so the result is 5."],"response_history":["Added 4 and 1 which made 5","5"],"rt":97882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":751838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8 plus 4 equals 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, 9 is subtracted from 12 to get 3.","explanation_history":["8 plus 4 equals 12. Since 12 is greater than 9 ","8 plus 4 equals 12. Since 12 is greater than 9, 9 is subtracted from 12 to get 3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":57910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":809750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"8","explain":true,"explanation":"Start ing with  8 plus 8 you get 7 and decrease by 1 for each new total until you get to 0.","explanation_history":["Starting with 8 plus 8 you get 7 and decrease by 1 for each new total until you get to 0."],"response_history":["8"],"rt":880078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1689834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":41958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1731798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":6198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1738001,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":7437,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1745445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"Since the total must equal 9, 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6.","explanation_history":["y","3 is subtracted form ","3 is subtracted form","3 is subtracted for","3 is subtracted fo","3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","S3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Si3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Sin3 is subtracted from 9 which equal s 6","Si nc3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since th3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the t3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the to3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the tot3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the tota3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total m3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total mu3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total mus3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must e3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must eq3 is sub tracted  from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equ3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equa3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equal3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equal 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equal 93 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equal 9,3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6","Since the total must equal 9, 3 is subtracted from 9 which equals 6."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":102832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1848283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It doesn't product every number less than 9.","explanation_history":["It doesn't product every number leaa","It  doesn't  product every number lea","It doesn't product every number less than 9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":97974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1946262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It doesn't produce every number less than 9.","explanation_history":["It doesn't product","It doesn't producr","It doesn't produce every number lea","It doesn't produce every number less than 9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":27172,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1973437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Y es","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"It can produce every number less than 9.","explanation_history":["Yes. It can produce every number less than 9.","Yes.It can produce every number less than 9.","YesIt can produce every number less than 9.","YeIt can produce every number less than 9.","YIt can produce every number less than 9.","It can produce every number less than 9."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":44269,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2017711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It can't produce every number less than 9.","explanation_history":["It can't preo","It can't pre","It can't produce every number less than 9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":20747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2038465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":46742,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2085211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"Inverse = N - 1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1","n-","n","Inverse = N - 1"],"rt":42485,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2127698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the f ormula f or the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"N - X","explain":true,"explanation":"X plus the inverse equals N. Or the inverse = N - X.","explanation_history":["The number plus the inverse equals "," plus the inverse equals ","X plus the inverse equals N. Or the inverse -","X plus the inverse equals N. Or the inverse = n -","X plus the inverse equals N. Or the inverse = n ","X plus the inverse equals N. Or the inverse = n","X plus the inverse equals N. Or the inverse = N - X."],"response_history":["N - X"],"rt":126207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2253908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 and N -1 are generators.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["% and ","% and","% an","% a","% ","%","5 and N -1 are generators."],"rt":514716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2768630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":27209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2795847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2804962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":56502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2861471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"This is only t rue if t he divisor is 1.","explanation_history":["This is only true if the divsor","This is only true if the divso","This is only true if the divs","This is only true if the divisor is 1."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":241211,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3102688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":52303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3154997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explai n in wor ds how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"I tested it and it's true but at this point my mind is beginning to get foggy.","explanation_history":["It ","It","I","I'm not sure why","I tested it and it's true but at this point my mind is beginning to get foggy."],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":576030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3731033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes","Never"],"rt":112178,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3843217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":7502,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3850721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"65 and getting older by the minute","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["65 and getting older by the minute"],"rt":19318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3870041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M. D., etc. "],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":4423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3874465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Calculus"],"rt":23474,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3897940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it  but not  often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":15911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3913856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":9595,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3923454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15- 0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":19240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3942696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3949600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definit ely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":16095,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3965696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":3525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3969223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":8711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3977935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":14351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3992287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I wasn't expecting the Spanish Inqusition.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I wasn't expecting the Spanish Inqusition."],"rt":31935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":4024223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]